翻譯: 夏 Amber B'S SOY
大家伙兒 早上好
Morning, campers.
有沒有人覺得這是個醉人的星期二呀
Anyone catch Tuesday boozeday this morning?
Hoda可激動了
Hoda was on fire.
站住 站住 Reed醫生
All right, Dr. Reed. Stop, stop.
校對: 揪頭發的朽
你身上有沒有帶肉制品
Do you have any meat products on your person?
怎么回事
What's going on?
我受夠了每次去救狗都被咬
What's going on is I'm sick of getting bit by dogs
后期: 大塊頭要冷靜
所以我要測試我的新護臂
every time I try to rescue them, so I'm testing my new armguard.
好吧 那你得要一只狗吧 來訓練
Right, you're gonna need a dog, aren't you, to train...
壓制: BB
這狗很生氣 是不是不大好
Oh. Is it bad that he's frothing?
Morgan 我們不能這樣做的好吧
We are not doing this, Morgan.
沒事兒 Tamra會保護我的
Look, Tamra's my fail-safe. Relax.
我有麻醉槍在手
I'll tranq his ass out.
病人馬上就來了
We have patients coming.
一會兒就行 可能好一會兒
It will take one second or seven dog seconds.
Reed醫生 就一下 拜托了
Just wait. Please, Dr. Reed.
Betsy 1 2 3 開始
Okay, Betsy. One, two, three.
- 放馬過來吧  - 不許放開這只狗
- Let him go. - I'm ordering you not to release him.
來吧 來吧
Come on, come on...
喔 喔 喔
Ah, oh, oh, ow!
快射呀 Tamra
There, Tamra! Fire!
不 你射偏了
Aah! No, you're missing it.
- 再射呀  - 馬上 馬上啦
- Fire again. - I'm trying! I'm trying!
繼續射 又射偏了
Keep shooting! You're missing...
好吧
Okay!
- 天哪  - 我已經不疼了
- Oh, my God. - I feel good now.
Morgan 我們該吸取什么教訓呢
Morgan, what have we learned from this?
明迪煩事多    第二季 第九集
電波誠譯
Lahiri醫生 我知道你生我氣是應該的
Dr. Lahiri, you have every right to be furious with me.
等一下 L醫生 我知道你聽到我講話了
Wait, Dr. L? I know you can hear me.
我買了你最喜歡的甜甜圈
I got your favorite doughnut,
撒熏肉屑的波士頓奶油
Boston cream with bacon shavings.
波士頓奶油是一種表面有巧克力和香草內餡的甜甜圈
現在可以原諒我了嗎
Now do you forgive me?
不 你瘋了嗎
No, my... Are you crazy?
好吧 L醫生 我知道
Dr. L, okay, I know...
你可能有點生氣或者你來月經了
You might be a little mad or maybe on your period.
我是對你有點生氣
You know what? I am a little mad at you.
我也正處于月經爆發狀態
And I'm a lot on my period.
你拿我的手機給我的暗戀對象發色情短信
You send sexual texts to my crush from my phone.
現在Cliff在和另一個女孩子約會
Now, Cliff's dating the girl down the hall and not me.
- 你瘋了嗎  - 這個問題沒法回答的啊
- Are you insane? - Well, that's impossible to answer.
瘋子一般都不知道他們自己是瘋的 L醫生
Insane people don't know they're insane, Dr. L.
還有 這個甜甜圈還可以吃的
This doughnut is still good, for the record.
好吧 Morgan 我是喜歡Cliff
Yes, Morgan, I like Cliff.
我喜歡你做的事嗎 不喜歡
Do I like how you went about it? No.
我喜歡把他的短信存手機里嗎
Do I like having his texts in my phone?
有點吧 有時候一晚上我要看兩遍
Kinda, sometimes I like it twice in the same night.
- 喔 天哪  – 沒錯
- Oh, my God. - Yeah.
等一下 等一下 Cliff
Hold, hold... Cliff.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hello.
- 天氣不錯 – 你好呀
- Nice day. - Hello.
嘿
Oh, hi.
恩 天氣不錯
Yeah. It is a beautiful day.
是的
Yeah.
- Heather怎么樣  – Heather很好呀
- How's Heather? - Heather's good.
今晚我打算帶她去
Yeah, uh, tonight, I'm taking her
看新的太陽馬戲團演出
to the new Cirque Du Soleil show
是關于電子游戲的歷史的
about the history of video games.
- Joystique(諧音joystick游戲手柄)  - 聽著挺有趣的
- Joystique. - Hmm, that sounds fun,
就跟你用牙齒
almost as fun as you taking
脫我的文胸一樣有趣嗎
my bra off with your teeth?
那是我短信里的原話
Oh. That is a direct quote from one of my texts.
- 你沒有刪掉嗎  - 沒有
- You didn't delete them? - I did not.
但是
But...
"但是"下面就沒有了
That's just the end of the sentence.
我沒刪掉
I-I did not delete them.
- 有沒有搞錯  - 還是哥們吧
- God. - Still friends?
不 Morgan 鬼才是你的哥們
No, we're not friends, Morgan.
我覺得你這人真不怎么樣
I think you are a bad person.
不 Cliff 別這樣說啊
No,  Cliff, take that back.
別這樣嘛
Take that back.
現在很少能在曼哈頓找到一家診所
It's so rare to find a practice in Manhattan these days
怎么說呢
with such a, I don't know,
有讓人舒心的醫生配置了
wholesome roster of doctors.
你 英國醫生 帥哥醫生
You, the British doctor, the handsome one.
帥哥 你不是已經說過我了嗎
Handsome one? You already said me.
我一直都有在我的媽咪博客上
You know, I've been singing your praises
贊頌你們呢
on my mommy blog.
真是多謝
Oh, thank you so much.
啊 Tamra
Aah! Tamra!
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
你以后不要在衛生間刮腿毛了
You cannot shave your legs in the bathroom anymore!
害我跌了個大跟頭
I just slipped in a puddle,
我屁股都快開花了
and I hurt my hip very badly.
- 快扶我起來 - 我不能在家里刮腿毛
- Help me up. - I couldn't shave at home.
Ray Ron把我家的衛生間改造成錄音棚了
Ray Ron turned our bathroom into a recording studio.
這樣 你以后都不要用這個衛生間了
You know what? You're banned from the bathroom.
你去對面馬路的
You have to use the bathroom
咖啡廳上廁所
across the way at the coffee shop.
那間咖啡廳不讓我用他們的廁所
I'm banned from that one.
當然啦 我也不是對所有人都那么喜歡
Of course, I'm not crazy about everyone here,
但是我覺得每個地方都有最少
but I guess every place has to have
一個這種人 對吧
at least one of them, right?
一個又吵又鬧大驚小怪的 沒錯
A mouthy drama queen? Yes.
高級合伙人們 我們該怎么處理預算盈余呢
Okay, senior partners, how do we spend the surplus?
其實 我有個主意
You know, I have an idea.
我覺得我們應該投資一間哺乳咨詢室
I think we should invest in a lactation consultant.
想想看
Think about it.
母乳喂養就像棒球一樣
You know what? Breast-feeding's like baseball.
知道得越少 就做得越好
The less you think about it, the better you do.
我有個主意
I have an idea.
我們去買一個金球獎現場的桌位吧
Oh, we gotta buy a table at the Golden Globes.
- 拜托  - 有我們 有<歡樂合唱團>劇組
- Oh, come on. - There's us, the cast of glee,
- 有<丑聞>劇組  - 大伙兒們
- the cast of scandal, the cast of... - Okay, senior partners?
怎么處置額外的利潤 我有個想法
I have an idea about what to do with the extra revenue.
與其等待病人上門
What if instead of waiting for the patients
不如我們主動去病人那兒
to come to us, we go to them?
我知道有輛車可以拿來改裝
I know this vehicle that we could fix up,
做成一個流動醫療站
turn into a mobile clinic.
等一下 等一下 你是想誆我們
Wait, wait, wait, you're just trying to scam us
買你朋友的派對大巴吧
into buying your friend's old party bus.
沒錯 它確實是輛派對大巴
Yes, it is a party bus,
我也不否認 我是在那輛車上丟掉了初夜
and yes, I did lose my virginity there.
但是我們把它改造一下 拆掉鋼管
But if we refurbish it, take down the pole...
Peter 我覺得你不該老想著喝酒狂歡的那檔子事
Peter, I think you shouldn't stick to thinking up drinking games.
我知道我很漂亮
Okay, just because I'm pretty
但不表示我是前臺好吧
does not mean I'm a receptionist.
那些助產員讓我轉達你們他們已經到了
Those midwives told me to tell y'all they're here.
走吧
Let's go.
最后說一遍 我們不要烘手機
For the last time, we're not getting hand dryers.
我更喜歡用紙巾
I like using paper towels too much.
我們不是為這個來的
That's not the reason for our visit.
你們也知道 Tracy Whitfield
As you all know, Tracy Whitfield
將會競選議員 作為紐約之城(較為政治的用語)
will be running for congress to represent our part
本區的代表
of the city of New York.
是紐約好不好
Okay, it's New York City, Pal.
我和Duncan都堅信他身上肩負著了
Duncan and I believe that he represents
這個行政區最大的希望
this district's greatest hope.
而且我們覺得他是黑人這點特別有型
And we think it's cool that he's black.
相當有型
Extremely cool.
所以你們應該不會介意
So we assumed you won't mind
我們在你們的辦公室里貼點海報
if we hang a few posters in your office.
我認識這人 我們以前都在達特茅斯讀書
Hey, I know that guy. We went to Dartmouth together.
達特茅斯 美國名校 以學生嗜酒著稱
- 這家伙很能喝的 - 達特茅斯
- That guy can drink. - Dartmouth?
他的競選綱領是什么 請Dave Matthews
What's his platform, hire Dave Matthews
Dave Matthews 美國搖滾歌手 熱衷政治
來重寫國歌嗎
to rewrite the national anthem?
- 還是算了吧  - 你們根本不知道他的立場
- I think we're good. - You don't even know what he stands for.
但我知道要是你們喜歡他 我們就不喜歡
Yeah, but I know if you guys like him, we don't.
- 再見了 Deslauriers  - 從哪來回哪去吧
- Good-bye, Deslauriers. - Yeah, bounce.
Duncan  我們回樓上
Come on, Duncan, let's go back upstairs
回我們的21世紀
to the 21st century.
那再見咯
Okay, smell you later.
Mindy
Hey, Mindy?
有空談兩句嗎
Could I talk to you for a second?
Peter 我現在真的很忙
You know, Peter, I'm really busy with work right now.
我沒時間聽你在這兒模仿Borat
I don't have time to listen to your Borat impression...
<Borat>2006年上映的一部美國喜劇電影
"我老婆"
"My wife."
我知道你和其他醫生們
I'm getting the vibe that you and the other doctors
都不是很欣賞我的想法
maybe don't respect my ideas.
沒有啊 你的想法挺不錯的
No, you have plenty of great ideas,
比如房車族周四
like trailer trash Thursday.
我知道我是C.P.P.
I know that I'm a C.P.P.,
狂歡派對首領
captain of the party patrol,
但是我想I.B.D.
but I wanna be I.B.D.,
參與商務決定
involved in business decisions.
我想要成為高級合伙人 S.P.
I wanna be a senior partner, S.P.
不 Peter 你是初級合伙人
Uh, no. Peter, you're a Junior partner.
比高級合伙人有型多了
That's so much cooler than senior partner
因為你是唯一的一個
'cause there's, like, only one of you.
我們對你也沒有什么期望
We have, like, no expectations for you.
比如說 我是雖然是個很好的領導
For instance, I'm a great leader,
但是我這輩子都搬不動重家具
but I can't move heavy furniture for the life of me.
這是要去哪兒
Where are we going?
因為我實在太嬌弱了
'Cause I'm, like, so petite, you know?
我上肢無力
I don't have the upper-body strength.
對話就這樣結束了嗎
Is that the end of the conversation?
耶
Yes!
瞧一瞧 看一看
Well, well, well, well, well.
看誰上了網絡博客
Look who's an Internet blog.
- 你戴了你的閱讀眼鏡  - 沒錯
- You wear reading glasses? - Yep.
這是那種從中間連起來的嗎
Oh, are those the kind that connect in the middle?
我姑姑Cora也有一副
My aunt Cora has them.
這眼鏡好紅啊 C醫生
They're really red, Dr. C.
好了 別管眼鏡了 聽著啊
Okay, enough with the glasses. Listen to this.
"除了
"Despite... des...
"除了名字之外 舒爾曼及合伙人診所
"Despite the name, Shulman & Associates
"象征著傳統價值觀的回歸
"Is a refreshing return to traditional values.
大部分醫生都心靈純潔 血統純正
Most of the doctors are pure of heart and pure of blood."
我是不是老說我心靈純潔 哈
Aren't I always saying I'm pure of heart, huh?
"Castellano醫生知道
"Dr. Castellano knows that the first hands
"碰觸珍貴的寶寶的第一雙手 應該是
"That touch your precious baby should be...
象牙白的"
Ivory white."
- 天哪  - 嗯
- Oh, my God. - Okay.
白色媽咪網
"Whitemommy.Com"?
什么鬼東西啊
What the hell's going on?
"對雅利安婦女來說
"It's often a hardship for an aryan woman
"找到合適的醫療是很困難的 尤其是在
"To find appropriate medical care on the island of..."
"猶哈頓"
"Jew-hattan"?
天哪 Danny
Oh, my God, Danny.
這是一個宣揚白人至上的網站
Uh-oh. This is a white power website.
C醫生 你總是被耍啊
Dr. C, you always getting played out.
不不不 我沒有被耍
No, no, no, no, I'm not getting played out here.
我告訴你們
I'll tell you what happened is
一定是什么東西弄混了
something got mixed up.
好吧 事情是這樣 這就是個小網站
Okay, these things happen. It's a fringe site.
沒多少人會看的
I'm sure not many people read it.
所有人回去工作
Everyone back to work.
但是我沒有 Mindy 你去哪啊
But I don't... Mindy, where are you going?
你要好好考慮自己的政治傾向了 朋友
You need to rethink your politics, my friend.
這是 我不 白色媽咪
This is... I didn't... whitemommy?
白色媽咪網
whitemommy.Com?
我知道Sarah是你們的家族名
I know that Sarah is a family name.
但是我一看到超聲波圖
Ever since I saw that first sonogram,
就覺得這個孩子該叫Katniss
I just thought "Katniss" For this baby.
總之 去問問你丈夫吧 看看他的想法
Anyway, ask your husband, see what he thinks.
- 嗯  - 幾個星期后見啦
- Mm-hmm. - See you in a couple weeks.
Danny
Danny.
- Danny Danny Danny Danny  - 咋了
- Danny, Danny, Danny, Danny. - Yeah.
我好像聽到接生員的聲音了
Why am I hearing the midwives?
我們絕對不能容忍
We will not tolerate the opinions
白色媽咪網的觀點
of whitemommy.Com.
我們可以理智地討論
We will tolerate intelligent debate,
但是我們不能忍受
but we will not tolerate intolerance
這所醫院的偏見
in this building.
- 我知道你看見我了  - 該死的
- I know you see me. - Damn it.
這群小賤人
Those little bitches.
愛是什么顏色
So what is the color of love?
搞什么名堂 Deslaurier
What the hell, Deslaurier?
- 你為什么要在這搞抗議  - 這不是抗議
- Why are you picketing us? - We are not picketing.
這是關于種族的熱烈討論
This is a vibrant discussion about race.
那又怎樣 我們每時每刻都在談種族呢
So what? We discuss race all the time.
就昨天 我們還討論
Just yesterday, we were talking about
Derek Jeter和Eli Manning誰更性感呢
who's hotter, Derek Jeter or Eli Manning.
Derek Jeter紐約洋基隊隊長 父親為非洲裔美國人
Eli Manning紐約巨人隊四分衛
Jeter贏了 完勝
Jeter won. Landslide.
- 不認識  - 你說笑吧
- Don't know who that is. - Are you kidding me?
- 你居然不認識  - Danny 別激動別激動
- You don't know... - Danny, it's okay, it's okay.
住手 住手
Stop, stop, stop.
- 不值得這么做  - 我得說 這個行為太無恥了
- It's not worth it. I would like to say this is outrageous.
我們醫院愛每個種族的人
This practice loves people of all races.
這話從你嘴里說出來 真有意思
Hmm, very interesting coming from you.
沒關系 我做了點調查 Jeremy Reed醫生
That's right, I did a little research, Dr. Jeremy Reed,
1980年出生于南非的約翰內斯堡
born 1980, Johannesburg, South Africa.
所有人現在上樓 重新部署
Everybody upstairs now. Let's regroup.
希特勒 3k黨
Hitler, the kkk,
舒爾曼及合伙人診所
Shulman & Associates.
這樣說太過了吧
Okay, that's crazy.
這位是Priscilla Lane
This is Priscilla Lane,
城里最好的公關顧問
the top PR consultant in the city.
她知道她在說什么
She knows what she's talking about.
她搞定了Taylor Swift的肇事逃逸案
She handled Taylor Swift's hit-and-run.
什么 我怎么不知道Taylor Swift
What? I didn't know that Taylor Swift had...
- 噢  - 沒錯
- Oh. - Yeah.
目前看來 你們可能受到驅逐和起訴
Now, look, your practice is in danger
醫院岌岌可危
of eviction, a lawsuit.
你們的醫療許可也會被重新評估
Your medical license is coming under review.
是時候制定戰略了
You need a strategy.
我是印度人 不可能有種族歧視的
I am Indian. I can't be racist.
拜托 你只和白人勾搭
Oh, please, you only hook up with white guys.
而我 約過每個種族的女人
I've hooked up with every race of woman.
居然說這種話 我和我的朝鮮朋友
How dare you? I went to second base
Justin就上了二壘
with my friend Korean Justin.
他的手超級小
His hands were so small.
襯托得我的胸很大
It made my boobs feel enormous.
你剛剛說的都是種族歧視
Everything you just said was racist.
公關顧問 真好笑
PR consultant. What a joke.
我只知道PR(公關)代表波多黎各
I remember when "PR" Meant "Puerto rican."
- 你還沒受到教訓嗎  - 你的表現太失禮了
Have you learned nothing? Now you're just trying to be offensive.
- 聽她說 - 我們不能這么說話
- Listen to her. - That's not how we talk.
- Danny  - 干嘛
- Danny? - Yeah?
既然你是博客的關注焦點
Since you are the focus of the blog,
我會對你進行一對一的媒體特訓
I will give you one-on-one media training
準備到時候應對訪問
to prep you for your interviews.
什么 我
What, me?
Mindy和你的護士Tamra
Mindy and your nurse Tamra
會發布一份公告
will issue a statement asserting
聲明自己很愛在這工作
that they love to work here.
還有別的非洲裔美國雇員嗎
Are there other African-American employees?
是的 Jerry 身材性感的老家伙
Yes, Jerry, the orderly with the hot body.
人家的名字叫Reggie好嗎
No, his name's Reggie.
沒有叫Jerry或者Reggie的人在這工作過
No one named Reggie or Jerry has ever worked here.
Mindy 你和Tamra去吃晚飯
Mindy, you and Tamra will go to dinner.
- 然后把聲明寫了  - 沒問題
- You will write a statement. - I am on it.
一家分量很足的高級餐廳
A fancy restaurant that still has big portions.
P醫生
Dr. P?
- 我需要建議  - 是嗎
- I need advice. - Oh, yeah?
Cliff說我是個壞人
Cliff said I was a bad person.
我說了讓你把短信刪掉的
Well, I told you to delete those text messages.
- 那我送他個禮物怎么樣  - 嗯哼
- Oh, what if I got him a gift? - Mm-hmm?
我有成百上千的
I have hundreds and thousands
Betamax錄像帶
of betas, like betamax tapes.
Betamax是索尼公司于1975年發行的一種錄像帶格式 之后被很快淘汰
聽起來雖然很不錯
As amazing as that sounds,
不過我不認為他想要禮物
I don't think he wants a gift.
- 他是個男人  - 嗯
He's a guy. Mm-hmm.
他大概只想狠狠揍你一頓
He probably just wants to beat the crap out of you.
看啊 剩下的食物
Look, guys, leftovers.
高級合伙人說
The senior partners said we support staff
我們后勤可以拿來吃了
could have at them.
L醫生
Dr. L.
嘿 Tamra 你來了
Hey. Hey, Tamra, you made it.
我已經點了餐 而且吃了所有開胃菜
I already ordered for us and ate all our appetizers.
還要再點嗎
Should we order more?
好啊 Larry醫生
What up, Dr. Larry?
我是Ray Ron 很高興認識你
I'm Ray Ron, pleased to meet your acquaintance.
嗨 Ray Ron
Ah, Ray Ron.
久仰大名
I've heard so much about you.
謝謝你把Tamra送過來
Thanks for dropping Tamra off.
是這樣的 Ray Ron 這其實是
Oh, you know, Ray Ron, this is actually
工作的事 我只訂了兩個人的位子
kind of a work thing, so I only got a table for two.
他不放心我一個人吃晚餐
He doesn't trust me to eat dinner alone
因為有一次 我吃飯的時候坐在Mandy Patinkin旁邊
because this one time, I ate next to Mandy Patinkin,
Mandy Patinkin美國演員 代表作<國土安全><犯罪心理>
他對我一見鐘情
and he fell in love with me.
靠 希望這里有龍蝦
Damn, I hope they have lobster here.
雖然我過敏 但是我愛它的價格
I'm real allergic, but I love how expensive it is.
呃 Tamra 我們的聲明
So, Tamra, our statement.
需要融合你鮮明的態度
It needs to combine your bold attitude
和我強烈的真實感
and my fierce realness.
一定會很
Gonna be kind of a...
有趣的 我想
Fun assignment, I think.
好吧 再試一次
All right, let's try this again.
假設我是一個記者
I'm going to be a reporter,
我要問你一些問題
and I'm going to ask you some questions.
155磅
155.
- 什么  - 是我臥推舉重的重量
- What? - That's what I bench.
不算重 但我能做十二組
It's not a lot, but I can do 12 reps.
十二組 那也不算很多好嗎
12? Sorry, that's not that many reps.
聽著 你需要學會在談話中話鋒一轉
Look, you need the skills to change the conversation.
我會話鋒一轉
I'll change the conversation.
你的專業就是個笑話 懂嗎
Your profession's a joke, okay?
如果有個最不值得尊重職業排行的話
When it comes to least respected jobs,
就是女模特
it goes male model,
強盜 公關顧問 沒了
mugger, PR person, nothing.
你真是個暴躁的混球
You're a grouchy bastard.
你這個冷血貪婪鬼
You're a cold-blooded vulture.
這樣話鋒一轉的風格你喜歡不
How do you like that for changing the conversation?
去你的 爛透了 閉嘴吧
Oh, God, you are so lame. Please shut up.
這家診所給了我
And the practice has given me the confidence
觸摸繁星的自信
to reach for the stars.
此番話我是摘抄自
I actually borrowed that line
一篇關于電腦夏令營的大學論文的
from a college essay about computer camp.
唷 這些炸雞寶貝兒真是贊到爆啊
Yo, these chicken tenderonis is tight as hell.
這是炸魷魚 白癡 魷魚
That's calamari, r-dub. You know, squid.
魷魚
Squid?
噢 我又不是傻逼鯨魚
Oh. I ain't no played-out whale.
喂 別在餐廳這么做 好嗎
Hey, you can't do that at a restaurant, okay?
Ray Ron 你沒有要去的地方嗎
Ray Ron, is there no place that you need to be?
- 沒事干嗎你  - 哦 對
- Something to do?  - Oh, yeah.
我要出去嗨兩發大麻
I'ma go outside and vaporize.
馬 上 回
B.R.B.
Tamra 喂 Tamra
Tamra? Hey, Tamra?
不好意思 我 我很不喜歡他
I'm sorry. I, like, hate him so much.
他根本就是個二流子
He's such a deadbeat,
根本就不像碧昂斯歌里面唱的那些帥哥
and not the hot kind that Beyonce sings songs about.
比較像布蘭妮歌里面唱的那樣
The kind that Britney sings songs about?
喂 打住 L醫生
Hey, hold up, Dr. L.
Ray Ron可能是有點沒教養
Ray Ron might be uneducated,
沒打過疫苗 腳趾有連趾
unvaccinated, and he has webbed feet...
惡
Ugh.
但是他尊重我
But he respects me.
我愛他
And I love him.
Tamra 我覺得你應該和
Tamra, I think that you need to be
那些和你比較像的人在一起
with someone more like you.
我告訴你
You know what?
你自己搞定那份聲明吧
You can finish that statement by yourself.
我要和Ray Ron回家
I'ma take Ray Ron home
讓他用腳給我做背部按摩
and make him massage my back with his messed-up feet.
Tamra 我已經告訴他們今天我生日了
Tamra, I already told them it was my birthday.
蛋糕要上了
There's cake coming.
嘿 你和所有種族的女孩都交往過嗎
Hey, have you really been with every race of girl?
差不多吧
Pretty much,
除了一種
except for one.
哪種呀
Which one?
關你什么事
None of your business.
是太平洋島上的人嗎
What... like pacific islander?
意大利人
Oh, God. Italian?
- 那可不  - 好了 拜托
- That's not...  - Okay, come on.
我現在想要邀請一位曾經受過
I'd now like to invite someone up who's experienced
舒爾曼及合伙人診所種族歧視的人加入我們
the racism of Shulman & Associates firsthand.
啥 Tamra
What? Tamra?
*反對婦產科*
*Against the obgs*
*一同唱首歌*
*We sing a song*
慢著 我成了種族主義者了
wait, I'm a racist now?
這是要搞群眾大會嗎
What, it's a rally now?
有請 Tamra
Now, sister Tamra,
你在舒爾曼及合伙人診所工作
you work at Shulman & Associates.
告訴大家 這兒和50年代阿拉巴馬州的伯明翰有什么相似之處
Tell us, how much is it like 1950s Birmingham, Alabama?
什么
What?
嗯 Lahiri醫生是說過
Well, Dr. Lahiri did say
我得單獨用一個衛生間
I had to use a separate bathroom.
是的 我說過
Yes, I did.
因為你把公用衛生間搞得一團糟
It was only because you were making a huge mess.
這位助產士認為所有種族
The midwives believe all ethnicities
都有權生兒育女 直到我們有
should procreate until we have
一張美麗的焦糖色臉蛋
one gorgeous caramel-colored race.
這是摘抄自你七年級突然頓悟
Is that from your seventh-grade diary
然后寫下的那篇日記的嗎
when you had that epiphany?
她說我應該甩掉我那白人男友
She said I had to dump my white boyfriend
然后找個和我更像的人
to get with someone more like me.
慢著 慢著 不是這樣的
Wait, wait, okay, no.
我指的是和她一樣又聰明又迷人的人
I only meant smart and attractive like she is.
你說他是二流子
You called him a deadbeat.
- 什么  他就是個二流子
- What?  - He is a deadbeat.
如果你們見過他 你們就知道了
If you knew him, you would understand.
你也覺得他是個二流子 不是嗎
You think he's a deadbeat, right?
不 我喜歡他 我喜歡所有人
No, I love him. I love everyone.
叫一個白人二流子又沒什么
And it's okay to call a white person a deadbeat...
- 不 很不妥  - "自命不凡"或"游手好閑"
- No, it's not.  - Or uppity or lazy.
好了 好了 夠了
Okay, okay, that's enough.
這么叫有什么錯 他就是 Danny
That's fine to call... Well, he is, Danny.
不 不 Tamra Tamra
No, no. Tamra, Tamra!
女士們先生們 舒爾曼及合伙人診所
Shulman & Associates, ladies and gentlemen,
一個隨便給人打標簽的地方
where it's okay to call people names.
我說 我們該掛Whitfield的海報的
I'm telling you, we should've hung those Whitfield signs.
那家伙挺酷的
He's a cool guy.
上大學時 他拿著一大簇蘑菇 然后
You know in college, he took a bunch of mushrooms and then...
嘿 Priss
Hey, Priss.
不好意思來晚了
I'm so sorry I'm late.
我的一個客戶向狗仔隊吐了口水
One of my clients just spit on a paparazzi.
不能告訴你是誰
I can't say who,
但他名字讀起來和"Shmalec Shmaldwin"押韻
but his name rhymes with "Shmalec Shmaldwin."
Danny 去收拾這個爛攤子吧
Danny, get up there and fix this.
嗯 我覺得他還沒準備好
Um, I actually don't think he's quite ready yet.
- 我可以去  - 萬萬不可 Peter
- I could go.  - Obviously not, Peter.
我們花了好多錢的 Danny沒問題
We've spent thousands. Danny's ready.
- 去吧  - 慢著 慢著
- Get up.  - Hold on, hold on.
慢著 我們有一位特別嘉賓
Hold on, we have a surprise speaker,
Daniel Castellano
Daniel Castellano,
白色媽咪網的封面人物
the cover boy for whititemommy.Com...
把麥給我 把麥給我
Just give me that. Give me that.
好了
Okay, o...
好 是這樣的 我可以花一整天
Okay, sit... Look, I can talk to you
跟你們談種族關系的話題
about race relations all day long,
但我要話鋒一轉了
but I'm gonna change the conversation.
你們知道從小到大我有多少黑人朋友嗎
You know how many black friends I had growing up?
四個 掐指一算
Four. Count 'em.
他都這么數自己的黑人朋友了
He counts his black friends, everybody.
這什么意思大家應該很清楚吧
That says it all right there.
Dummy
Dummy.
你話鋒一轉的時候
You don't change the conversation
不要告訴別人你在轉話鋒
by telling people you're changing the conversation.
哦 那你當時應該告訴我
Well, I wish you'd have told me that
而不是和我做愛
instead of having sex with me.
噢
Ooh.
- 我要走了  - Priss Priss Priss 別走
- I'm going.  - Priss, Priss, Priss, don't go.
- Priss  - 一開始是種族主義
- Priss.  - First, it's racism.
現在呢 變成了職場不正當性行為
Now, it's awkward sexual misconduct in the workplace.
我可能有點過時了 但感覺怎么就那么惡心呢
Call me old-fashioned. I find this a little weird.
難道你們不愿意在一個
Wouldn't you guys prefer to give birth
更體貼的醫院生孩子嗎
in a place that's more sensitive,
比如樓上一層
maybe one floor up?
慢著 這就是你的目的所在嗎
Wait a minute. Is that what this is about?
你想搶我們的生意
You wanna take over our business?
放尊重點
How dare you?
這是一場關于種族主義的抗議
This is a discussion of racism.
Cliff
Cliff.
- 等等等  - 你想要什么
- Wait, wait, wait.  - What do you want?
我知道你只想從我這得到一樣東西
I know there's only one thing that you want for me
我現在就給你
And I'm here to give it to you.
- 揍我一頓  - 啥 不
- Kick my ass.  - What? No.
- 拜托  - 早料到你會這么說
- Come on.  - I knew you were gonna say that.
胖虎
Big meat.
這是胖虎 他會給我來一頓
Big meat here, he's gonna give me what I deserve.
他欠我的
He owes me.
Tookers先生幫我搬過家
Mr. Tookers helped me move.
兩次 好嗎
Twice, okay?
后退 不 這是為了你好
Back up. No, this is for you.
別留情面 只要不打牙齒就好
Give it to me hard, just not in the teeth
我靠這微笑吃飯的
'cause my smile's my moneymaker.
- 不要打人  - 來吧
- No, stop, nobody's hitting anybody.  - Do it!
噢
Oh.
啊 搞毛啊
Aw. What the hell?
跑 跑 跑 去布朗克斯動物園
Run, run, go. Go to the Bronx zoo.
晚些找你
I'll call you later.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
謝謝 Duncan 引用Langston Hughes的
Thank you, Duncan, for those illuminating words
Langston Hughes美國黑人文學舉足輕重的作家
這些發人深省的話語
from Langston Hughes.
各位 我們有一個激動人心的消息
We have an exciting update, everyone.
好幾輛新聞采訪車正在趕來
Several news vans are on their way
傳播我們的想法
to help spread our message.
- 這下好了  - 我們會被釘十字架的
- Great.  - We're gonna get crucified.
要是Olivia Pope在就好了
If only Olivia Pope was here.
Olivia Pope <丑聞>女主角 保護機密的危機處理專家
噢 Tracy Whitfield本人來了
Oh, and Tracy Whitfield himself is here
他將表達我們對凌辱的憤怒
to lend his voice to our chorus of outrage.
但是Peter 在達特茅斯的時候
But, Peter, you know Tracy Whitfield
你就認識Tracy Whitfield
from the university of "Dart-mouth."
是啊 我今天起碼說了五遍了
Yeah, I've said that, like, five times today.
就是他阻止我在胳膊上烙印的
He's the one that stopped me from getting my arm branded.
- 去跟他談談  - 搞定這攤事吧
- Go talk to him.  - Make this go away.
求你了 Peter 幫幫我們
Please, Peter, help us.
你們要我幫你們
You need my help?
是的
Yes, we do.
初級合伙人要幫助
The Junior partner is gonna help this...
我們需要幫助 求你了
We need help. Please go do it.
- 求你了 求你了 很對不起  - 好啦 放輕松
- Please, please. We're so sorry.  - Okay, relax.
- 我搞定  - 好的
- I'm on it.  - Okay.
嘿 唷 Whitfield
Hey, yo, Whitfield!
嗨 嗨
Hey. Hey.
糟了
Oh.
那人不是我朋友 我認錯人了
That is not my friend. I made a horrible mistake.
什么 你搞什么鬼啊
What... what the hell's wrong with you?
Peter 這真是十足的種族歧視
Peter! Okay, that was very racist.
Cliff 我不該拿色情短信
Cliff, I should never have duped you
來逗你玩
into a sexual text conversation.
是我不好
I'm sorry.
行了 沒事
Okay, thank you.
不過我覺得也沒什么
I'm also a little not.
別再提這件事了 行么
Could've just ended it there.
不是 我這么說是因為我覺得Mindy真的喜歡你
No, I'm not sorry because Mindy really liked you.
而且我覺得你也對她有想法
And I think you had a case of the hornies for her.
疼
Oh.
我才沒有什么"想法"
I'm not really crazy about "Case of the hornies,"
再說 我和Heather已經在一起了
and I'm with Heather now.
聽著 我沒有覺得
And look, I don't think
你人不好 你明白我的意思吧
that you're a bad person, okay?
我就是 只是 感覺你在某種程度上
I just... I just... I find you to be somewhat...
讓人受不了
Unbearable.
是的 你們應該氣憤
Yes, some of you are angry.
我們絕不能容忍歧視
We cannot tolerate discrimination,
我會讓這些醫生走人的
and I will shut these doctors down.
我解釋一下 每次我都是醉得不省人事
In my defense, I was drunk
的時候和我以為是他的人出去玩的
every time I hung out with the guy I thought that was.
我打算稍微有點尊嚴
Well, I'm going to do the dignified thing
我也去抗議了
and join the protesters.
我們應該把Priscilla叫回來
Maybe we need to get Priscilla to come back.
不嘛
No?
明天是整個區
Tomorrow, across the district.
明年就是整個議會
Next year, to the halls of congress.
- 我過去一下 - 然后直到全國上下
- Excuse me, guys. - Maybe all the way to the White House!
讓我們一起努力吧
Who's with me?
我死也沒想過 我有生之年
I never thought I'd live to see
還能看見第二個黑人當上總統
a second black President.
Tamra
Hey, Tamra.
我一想到你誤以為我
It makes me sick to think
也種族歧視 我就生氣
that you might think I'm a racist.
我知道你不是 L醫生
I know you're not racist, Dr. L.
那你為什么那樣
Then why are you doing this?
- 你感覺上有點... - 反猶太么 我知道
- You are a little... - Anti-semitic, I know.
誰知道 沒準我以后會嫁給個猶太人
But you know what? I'm probably gonna marry one.
不是 你工作上
No, you can be condescending
對下屬總是盛氣凌人
to the people under you at work.
總之 感覺上你就是翻版的<唐頓莊園>
Something, you get a little Downton Abbey.
你還看過<唐頓莊園>  - 你看
You've seen Downton Abbey? - See?
你就是看不起人
That's condescending. Yeah.
你跟我說不要跟Ray Ron約會
So when you told me not to date Ray Ron,
他在精神上改變了我對世界的認知
a man who redefines my universe spiritually
而且他脖子有傷 算是殘疾人
and gets disability 'cause of his neck,
我覺得你簡直不尊重人
I just felt disrespected.
好了 別說了 明白了
Okay, okay, all right.
Tamra 聽我說 我從來沒有看不起任何人
Listen, Tamra, I do not look down on anyone.
對不起
I'm so sorry.
好吧 親愛的
Okay, girl.
我就是看不上Ray Ron
I do look down on Ray Ron.
我會試著多了解他的
I'll try to get to know him better.
我們絕不能允許一些醫生將讓我們退步回一百年前
We can't let these doctors turn the clock back a hundred years.
一方面是 我可離不開智能手機
For one thing, I'd miss my smartphone.
手機在我在
Gotta have my smartphone.
天哪 真是聽夠了 我先走了
All right, I've had enough of this. Excuse me.
我們需要讓像舒爾曼及合伙人診所
We need to send a message
那樣的種族歧視的人知道
that hatemongers like Shulman & Associates
他們會像奴隸主和種族隔離者一樣完蛋的
will disappear like slavery and apartheid.
這不僅僅是我們的聲音
This message is more than...
不好意思 Whitfield先生
Excuse me, Mr. Whitfield?
您介意我說兩句么
Do you mind if I say something?
嗯 把話筒給她
Um... Just give her the mic.
她正好給抗議者來點火上澆油
She'll give us more to protest.
閉嘴
Shut up.
是 我閉嘴
Uh, sure.
謝謝
Thank you.
是的 我知道你們現在非常氣憤
Okay, I know you're all very angry right now.
下去吧
Shame.
我只有一句話想說
I just wanna say one thing,
我是Mindy Lahiri
which is my name is Mindy Lahiri,
我并不是一個種族歧視者
and I am not a racist.
當然 有時候我也會拿這個打打趣
Sure, I tell edgy jokes sometimes,
而人們也都喜歡聽
but people really like that.
開開心有助身心健康 現在經濟這么不好
It's good for morale in this economy.
說什么呢你
Are you kidding me?
但是 更重要的是
Moreover... More importantly,
舒爾曼及合伙人診所不是這樣的
Shulman & Associates are not racists.
我們幫助貧窮的婦女
We help women who are poor,
無論她們的種族 即便她們沒有保險
who are uninsured, of almost every ethnicity.
實際上 我們有個醫生
In fact... Oh, one of our doctors,
Danny Castellano醫生 今天早上告訴我
Dr. Danny Castellano, he told me this morning
他睡過的女人
that he has had sex with women
基本上涵蓋每個種族
of almost every single race.
- 別指名道姓 - 正好 他就是
- Don't say my name. - There he is, right there.
Danny Castellano
Danny Castellano.
- 你這是  - 你上過差不多所有種族的女的
- What are you do... - you've had sex with a woman of every race.
這是個人隱私
That's personal.
一點也不覺得熱淚盈眶么
Doesn't that bring a tear to your eye?
沒有 那好吧
No? Okay.
嗯 我們還有位醫生
Um, another doctor of ours
是移動醫療站的發起人
is spearheading a mobile health unit initiative.
每個月一次 我們都會開車到
Once a month, our practice will take a van,
到低收入社區
and we're gonna go to low-income areas,
去幫助有需要的婦女
and we're gonna help women in need.
實際上 如果我沒記錯 其中有一部分地區
Actually, some of the areas, I think,
就在您所在的行政區 Whitfield先生
are in your district, Mr. Whitfield.
是吧 有關聯哦
So, um, connection.
我所要說的是舒爾曼及合伙人診所
The point is Shulman & Associates...
絕沒有種族歧視
Not racists.
謝謝各位
Thank you very much.
Whitman 2014
Whitman 2014.
- 是Whitfield  - Whitfield
- Whitfield.- Whitfield.
對不起
Sorry.
我說了你上床的事情是不是不太好
Was it okay that I mentioned your sex partners?
- 是的 我不喜歡  - 哦
No, I didn't like that. - Okay.
我是不是太 好吧
Wow. Was it... okay.
我們的行政區實際上正需要你們的移動醫療站
Our district could actually use that mobile medical unit.
適當適時地放下武器
You know, part of fighting for justice
接受橄欖枝
is knowing when to put down your weapons
也是在伸張正義
and accept an olive branch.
不不 等會兒
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
這才不是什么橄欖枝
This is not an olive branch.
她扔給你的是奴隸主的鞭子
This is a master's whip they're handing you.
哥們兒 聽著
Ooh, hey, listen up, man.
你有點讓我覺得不爽了
You're starting to make me feel uncomfortable, all right?
別浪費我的時間了
And you're kind of wasting my time.
他們根本不是種族主義者
These people are barely racist.
聽我說
Wait...
移動醫療站真是
So the mobile health idea kind of...
該怎么說 救了我們一命啊
I don't know, I think it saved the day.
你打算怎么好好謝謝我
What would be a good thank-you gift for me?
不如直接升我為高級合伙人
What about making me senior partner?
- 好啊 - 牛鼻
- Fine. - Noice!
我也要做高級合伙人
And I'ma be senior partner too.
你不是 你個小護士 快回去上班
No, you're the nurse. Go back up to work.
別再折騰了 Tamra
You wasted a lot of our time, Tamra.
沒問題 走 回去
All right, let's get back.
Mindy 你好
Hey, Mindy. Hi.
你好 我就是想跟你說
Hi, I just wanted to tell you
我非常欣賞你的激情
that I really admire your passion.
謝謝 嗯
Thank you. Yeah.
你讓我想起了丘吉爾夫人
You remind me of Winston Churchill.
沒錯 你的一言一行都很像
Yeah, the way you speak, the way you walk.
別說了
Okay.
我希望進一步了解
And I'd love to hear more
一些你們對移動醫療站的建設
about that mobile medical unit you got.
- 真的  - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
不如我們哪天吃飯的時候細談
Well, maybe we can talk more about it over dinner sometime.
好啊 聽起來不錯
Sure. That'd be great.
- 那我把Tyra叫上  - 誰
- I'll bring Tyra. - Who?
Tyra Banks 我倆約會呢
Tyra Banks. She and I are dating.
- 我的女朋友  - 呵呵
- She's my girlfriend.  - Okay.
你走吧 我沒時間跟你說這個
Get out of here. I don't have time for this.
好吧
Okay.
高級合伙人
Yes, senior partner.
初高級合伙人
Junior senior partner.
試用期
Probationary.
你和Priscilla談過了么
Have you talked to Priscilla?
沒有 還不太想
Nah. Not feeling it.
她是這么說的
That's what she told me.
好啊 Jerry
Hey, Jerry.
早上好 L醫生
Good morning, Dr. L.
哎呀 不用激動
All right, relax.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組